Find the truth.
Fear Street: 1978 is a horror, mystery film directed by Leigh Janiak.
In 1978, two rival groups at Camp Nightwing must band together to solve a
terrifying mystery when horrors from their towns' history come alive.
Ziggy Berman, played by Sadie Sink.
Cindy Berman, played by Emily Rudd.
Alice, played by Ryan Simpkins.
Tommy Slater, played by McCabe Slye.
C. Berman / Adult Ziggy, played by Gillian Jacobs.
Deena, played by Kiana Madeira.
Fear Street Part Two: 1978 (titled onscreen as Fear Street 1978) is a 2021
American supernatural slasher film directed by Leigh Janiak.
It is the second installment in the Fear Street trilogy, with a script co-written by Janiak and
Zak Olkewicz from a story by Janiak, Olkewicz and Phil Graziadei, based on R.
Stine's book series of the same name.
Primarily set in the summer of 1978, the film follows a group of teens at Camp Nightwing as
they face a deadly killing spree connected to the dark past of Shadyside.
It stars Sadie Sink, Emily Rudd, Ryan Simpkins, McCabe Slye, Ted Sutherland, Gillian
Jacobs, Kiana Madeira, Benjamin Flores Jr., and Olivia Scott Welch.
Produced by Chernin Entertainment, a film adaptation of Fear Street began
development at 20th Century Fox in 2015, with Janiak hired in 2017.
Filming for the trilogy took place back-to-back from March to September 2019 in
Georgia, with the intention of a theatrical release beginning June 2020.
However, due to the COVID-19 pandemic and the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney, Chernin Entertainment
ended their distribution deal with 20th Century Studios and sold rights to Netflix in August 2020.
Fear Street Part Two: 1978 premiered at the Los Angeles State Historic Park on July 8, 2021, and
was released by Netflix on July 9, 2021 a week after the first film Part One: 1994.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and is
considered to be the best film of the trilogy.
The final installment, Part Three: 1666, was released on July 16.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
summer camp, 1970s, curse, teenage girl.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.